<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mPerf User Guide on MD2K::software</title>
    <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mPerf User Guide on MD2K::software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, MD2K; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Participant User Guide</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg-phone/</guid>
      <description>What to Do Each Day  Wear the wrist sensors and carry the smartphone with you. Every 2-3 hours, check to confirm the phone is collecting data. Try to achieve at least 12 hours of data collection each day. Complete surveys on the phone when prompted. Charge phone and wrist sensors every night.  Wrist Sensors How to Use Wear the wrist sensors as you would wear a watch or FitBit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Participant User Guide</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg/</guid>
      <description>Devices You Will Wear and Carry Wrist Sensors  Motionsense HRV Wrist Sensor    These wrist sensors are very much like smart watches or FitBits. (You may still wear a FitBit or other activity trackers or watches alongside the study-provided sensors.) These wrist sensors gather data from your wrist/arm movements and transmit it via Bluetooth to the cell phone. If the wrist sensor is malfunctioning, please contact the Field Manager to get a replacement as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Software How-To: Admins &amp; Field Managers</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/field-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/field-managers/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Hardware Suite  Wrist Sensors Smartphone Location Beacons  How to Charge the Hardware How to Clean the Hardware mPerf Study App Overview How to Install/Update Apps How to Pair/Unpair a Wrist Sensor  Hardware Suite  2 Wrist Sensors 1 Smartphone (mCerebrum software installed) 2 Location Beacons 1 Multi-Device Charger 2 Wrist Sensor Charging Cables 1 Smartphone Charging Cable  Phone carrier and Participant ID can be found written on the outside of the envelope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf User Guide - Sensors Overview</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/sensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/sensors/</guid>
      <description>Sensors The mCerebrum software platform is configurable for a wide variety of mobile and wearable sensors. This page shows an overview of the sensors currently integrated with the software for the mPerf project.
Motionsense HRV Wrist Sensor  Motionsense HRV Wrist Sensor   Motionsense HRV is a wearable wrist sensor that integrates accelerometer, gyroscope, and magnetometer measurements. This can be used to track hand gestures and monitor activities such as smoking, eating, and brushing teeth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>