<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mPerf User Guide on MD2K::software</title>
    <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mPerf User Guide on MD2K::software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, MD2K; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf AT&amp;T Phone Setup</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-setups8a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-setups8a/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Connecting to a WiFi Network Migrating From Your Old Phone Changing the Default Language Setting Up Your Google Account Setting Up Your Work or Personal Email Adjusting Device Protection Features Which Apps Are Needed? Which Utilities Are Needed? Backing Up Files From Your Phone Adjusting Date and Time  Connecting to a WiFi Network To access WiFi settings:
1) Open the Settings app by tapping the Settings icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Lab Study: Admin</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/lab-study-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/lab-study-managers/</guid>
      <description>Overview When a participant is finished with the lab study, please complete the following steps to sync the data to the cloud, shut down all applications, back up the data on a computer, and prepare the phone for the next participant.
IMPORTANT NOTE: The data files that are recorded by the phone are one hour in length before they are completed and a new file is started. This takes place at the top of every hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Participant User Guide</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg-phone/</guid>
      <description>Contents  What to Do Each Day Wrist Sensors Location Beacons Phone App  Data Collection Sensor Data Quality Pause Data Collection Data Collection Duration Fitness and Work Duration Tracking Workplace Annotation  Chest Belt (optional) How to Charge the Devices  What to Do Each Day  Wear the wrist sensors and carry the smartphone with you. Every 2-3 hours, check to confirm the phone is collecting data. Try to wear the sensors during all waking hours, except when there is risk of the sensors getting wet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Participant User Guide</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/pg/</guid>
      <description>Devices You Will Wear and Carry Wrist Sensors  Motionsense HRV Wrist Sensor    These wrist sensors are very much like smart watches or FitBits. (You may still wear a FitBit or other activity trackers or watches alongside the study-provided sensors.) These wrist sensors gather data from your wrist/arm movements and transmit it via Bluetooth to the cell phone. If the wrist sensor is malfunctioning, please contact the Field Manager to get a replacement as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Software How-To: Admins &amp; Field Managers</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/field-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/field-managers/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Hardware Suite  Wrist Sensors Smartphone Location Beacons  How to Charge the Hardware How to Clean the Hardware mPerf Study App Overview  Data Collection Sensor Data Quality Pause Data Collection Data Collection Duration Fitness and Work Duration Tracking Workplace Annotation  How to Leave a Study How to Join a Study How to Install/Update Apps How to Add/Remove a Wrist Sensor  Submit bug reports and feature requests</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Study: iOS to Android Migration</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-ios2android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-ios2android/</guid>
      <description>Tips for Switching from iOS to Android Best Method Use Smart Switch (app already installed on Study Phone)
If Smart Switch is unavailable, follow these steps:  If you use Gmail, Google Calendar, Google Photos, Google Drive, and Google Maps, install those apps on Android and sign in using Google account. Use Google Drive to copy over contacts, photos, videos, and calendars.  Contact and calendars  Install Google Drive on iOS device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf T-Mobile Phone Setup</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-setups8t/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-setups8t/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Connecting to a WiFi Network Migrating From Your Old Phone Changing the Default Language Setting Up Your Google Account Setting Up Your Work or Personal Email Adjusting Device Protection Features Which Apps Are Needed? Which Utilities Are Needed? Backing Up Files From Your Phone Adjusting Date and Time  Connecting to a WiFi Network To access WiFi settings:
1) Open the Settings app by tapping the Settings icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf User Guide - Sensors Overview</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/sensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/sensors/</guid>
      <description>Sensors The mCerebrum software platform is configurable for a wide variety of mobile and wearable sensors. This page shows an overview of the sensors currently integrated with the software for the mPerf project.
Motionsense HRV Wrist Sensor  Motionsense HRV Wrist Sensor   Motionsense HRV is a wearable wrist sensor that integrates accelerometer, gyroscope, and magnetometer measurements. This can be used to track hand gestures and monitor activities such as smoking, eating, and brushing teeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mPerf Verizon Phone Setup</title>
      <link>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-setups8v/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://software.md2k.org/howto/mperf/phone-setups8v/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Connecting to a WiFi Network Migrating From Your Old Phone Changing the Default Language Setting Up Your Google Account Setting Up Your Work or Personal Email Adjusting Device Protection Features Which Apps Are Needed? Which Utilities Are Needed? Backing Up Files From Your Phone Adjusting Date and Time  Connecting to a WiFi Network To access WiFi settings:
1) Open the Settings app by tapping the Settings icon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>